brightredbooks.net 2017-05-29

# BrightRed Publishing. Privacy Policy

Bright Red Publishing Ltd will use the personal information you may supply on this website to provide you with sales and marketing information based on your choices and to ensure that the content and services that we offer are tailored to your needs and interests. We may keep your information for a reasonable period for these purposes. We may share your information with our service providers and agents for these purposes.

**PRIVACY**

All orders made through <http://www.brightredpublishing.co.uk/> are processed through Paypal. PayPal’s privacy policy can be viewed here: <https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>.

**Data Protection Information**

We are aware that you are concerned about the protection of the personal information you give to us. We take these concerns very seriously. Please carefully read this Privacy Policy, it will help you understand what happens to your personal data.

**Information we collect from you**

When you order a product online or register with the Digital Zone, by telephone, fax or post, or email or telephone us with a query, we collect personal data about you directly (including your name, address, telephone and email address).

**What happens to my personal data?**

We do not pass your personal information onto third parties.

We use the personal data that you directly provide to supply you with the products you chose and to maintain records of your access to, and use of, online services.

By registering for an online service, buying products online or by submitting your details for other purposes, e.g. writing reviews, providing feedback or registering for our newsletter, you consent to the collection and processing of your personal data as described above.

If you have any queries regarding Bright Red Publishing’s use of your personal data then please contact us at [info@brightredpublishing.co.uk](mailto:info@brightredpublishing.co.uk).

**Will I be contacted?**

From time to time, we may contact you with information relating to the goods and services featured on www.brightredpublishing.co.uk.

Please note that you can stop receiving this information at any time by emailing [info@brightredpublishing.co.uk](mailto:info@brightredpublishing.co.uk) and using "UNSUBSCRIBE" as your subject line.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Occasionally, it may be necessary for Bright Red Publishing to make changes or alterations to this Privacy Policy. You are advised that it is your responsibility to check the Bright Red Publishing website for such changes.

Your order is covered by the Privacy Policy in force at the time you make your order.
